http://techsail.com/privacy-policy/

HomeProducts Sailfish Yacht AnalyzerTechsail PolarTechsail NMEA ServerTechsail NAVTEXMOB Search LightDownloadsSupport Sea ChartFAQsBug ReportDocumentationPrivacy PolicyAbout Us Our CompanyContact UsPartners
Privacy Policy
It is Techsail´s aim that all persons whose personal data is processed by Techsail shall at all times feel confident that the person’s privacy is respected and that due care is taken regarding his or her personal data. Techsail has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
By visiting techsail.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: techsail.com.
Our site’s registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer’s contact information is used to create unique serial numbers and contacts to the visitor when necessary.
Links: This site contains links to other sites. Techsail is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
Ads: We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site. Our site does not use cookies. We do not have access to any information about you from cookies you might receive while visiting our site.
CORRECT/UPDATE – CONTACT
Disputes arising in connection with the privacy statement will be resolved by our web site’s customer service representative. If you have any questions regarding our personal data processing, you are welcome to contact us.
Email: info@techsail.com
